His aim is unrivaled.
Last Shoot Out is a western, action, thriller film directed by Michael Feifer.
Soon after a newlywed learns that her husband had her father shot
down, she flees from the Callahan ranch in fear.
She's rescued by a gunman who safeguards her at a remote outpost as he
staves off her husband's attempts to reclaim his bride.
Twigs, played by Jay Pickett.
Jody, played by Michael Welch.
Jocelyn Miller Callahan, played by Skylar Witte.
Blair Callahan, played by Bruce Dern.
Billy, played by Brock Harris.
Last Shoot Out is a 2021 American western film directed by Michael Feifer,
and starring Michael Welch, Cam Gigandet and Bruce Dern.
The tone is emotional and intense.